Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- United Board for Christian Colleges in China Consolidated General File, 1947-1955; Series II
  - American Medical Association, 1953-1957, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 736,737)
  - American Mission to Lepers - Anderson, E., 1948-1958 (Box 29, Folder 738)
  - Anderson, S. R., 1951-1955 (Box 29, Folder 739)
  - Andrews - Anes, 1946-1957 (Box 29, Folder 740)
  - Ang - Angle, 1949-1958 (Box 29, Folder 741)
  - Angulo, Cooney, March Ouchterloney, 1957 Sep 19-1958 (Box 29, Folder 742,743)
  - Anspach - Armstrong, H., 1946-1957 (Box 29, Folder 744)
  - Armstrong, S. - Arnhold, 1953-1958 (Box 29, Folder 745)
  - Arnold, Charles H., 1946-1956 (Box 29, Folder 746)
  - Arnup, Harold L., 1947-1952 (Box 30, Folder 747,748)
  - Arnup, Jesse H., 1945-1956 (Box 30, Folder 749,750)
  - Ascano, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 751)
  - Asher, Eva M., 1947-1952 (Box 30, Folder 752-757)
  - Ashmead, 1947-1957 (Box 30, Folder 758)
  - Asian Christian Colleges Association (London), 1954-1958 (Box 30, Folder 759-761)
  - Asia Colleges Newsletter, 1955-1958 (Box 30, Folder 762)
  - Asia Foundation, 1954-1958 (Box 30, Folder 763)
  - Aske, Sigurd, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 764)
  - Associated Boards for Christian Colleges in China: Certificate of Dissolution, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 765)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 766)
  - Association of Christian Schools and Colleges, Manila, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 767)
  - Atherton - Atkins, 1945-1957 (Box 30, Folder 768)
  - Atkinson - Atwood, 1946-1958 (Box 30, Folder 769)
  - Au, David W. K., 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 770)
  - Audio-visual Center, Nanking - Audit: Fukien Christian University, 1948, 1945-1949 (Box 30, Folder 771)
  - Audits: Fukien Christian University, 1949 Jun - Ginling College, 1948 Jun (Box 30, Folder 772)
  - Audits: Ginling College, 1949 Jun - Harvard-Yenching Institute, 1951 Jun (Box 30, Folder 773)
  - Audits: Hua Chung University, 1949 Jun - Hwa Nan College, 1951 Jun (Box 30, Folder 774)
  - Audits: University of Nanking, 1947 Jun - Princeton-Yenching Foundation, 1946 Jun (Box 30, Folder 775)
  - Audits: Princeton-Yenching Foundation, 1948 Jun - Shantung Christian University, 1948 Jun (Box 31, Folder 776)
  - Audits: Shantung Christian University, 1949 Jun - West China Union University, 1947 Jun (Box 31, Folder 777)
  - Audits: West China Union University, 1948 Jun - United Board, 1947 Jun (Box 31, Folder 778)
  - Audits: United Board, 1950 Jun - 1951 Jun (Box 31, Folder 779)
  - Audits: United Board and Constituent Colleges, 1952-1958 (Box 31, Folder 780-797)
  - Audits: Yenching University, 1946 Jun-1948 Jun (Box 31, Folder 798)
  - Audits: Yenching University, 1949 Jun-1951 Jun (Box 32, Folder 799)
  - Audits: Yenching College for Women, 1946 Jun-1951 Jun (Box 32, Folder 800)
  - Avann - Babcock, 1947-1958 (Box 32, Folder 801)
  - Bade - Ballard, 1946-1957 (Box 32, Folder 802)
  - Ballou - Bam, 1945-1955 (Box 32, Folder 803)
  - Band, William, 1945-1957 (Box 32, Folder 804)
  - Banfield - Bangerter, 1947-1957 (Box 32, Folder 805)
  - Banister Trust Fund, History of, 1927-1938 (Box 32, Folder 806)
  - Banister Trust Fund, 1945-1957 (Box 32, Folder 807,808)
  - Bank of China - Barker, 1947-1957 (Box 32, Folder 809)
  - Barnes, William J., 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 810)
  - Barnett, Eugene E., 1950-1958 (Box 32, Folder 811,812)
  - Barr, H. - Barr, John S. Ruth, 1949-1957 (Box 32, Folder 813)
  - Barr, T. - Barstow, 1948-1957 (Box 32, Folder 814)
  - Barthelmeus, Kurt, 1938-1954 (Box 32, Folder 815-817)
  - Bates, M. Searle, 1948-1957 (Box 32, Folder 818)
  - Bauer - Beardsley, 1947-1957 (Box 32, Folder 819)
  - Beaver - Beebe, 1951-1958 (Box 32, Folder 820)
  - Beeby, H. D., 1952-1955 (Box 32, Folder 821,822)
  - Beech, Joseph and Miriam, 1946-1957 (Box 32, Folder 823)
  - Bell - Bentley, 1947-1957 (Box 32, Folder 824)
  - Berea United Church - Besse, 1949-1958 (Box 32, Folder 825)
  - Bethesda Foundation - Bevans, 1946-1957 (Box 32, Folder 826)
  - Bien - Bishop, 1952-1958 (Box 32, Folder 827)
  - Blaine Bequest (Anita McCormick Blaine), 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 828-831)
  - Blair Estate (Mary Barbour Blair), 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 832)
  - Blair, M. B. - Bocker, 1947-1958 (Box 33, Folder 833)
  - Bodo - Boone Library School, 1943-1955 (Box 33, Folder 834)
  - Boorman, Howard L., 1952-1955 (Box 33, Folder 835)
  - Boring, Alice M., 1946-1955 (Box 33, Folder 836)
  - Boring, E. - Bowles, 1947-1955 (Box 33, Folder 837)
  - Boynton, Grace M., 1947-1955 (Box 33, Folder 838)
  - Brady - Bridges, 1950-1957 (Box 33, Folder 839)
  - Brigg, Horace, 1955-1958 (Box 33, Folder 840)
  - Bright - Bronk, 1945-1958 (Box 33, Folder 841)
  - Brown, Charles H., 1947-1956 (Box 33, Folder 842-845)
  - Brown, F. - Brown, W., 1946-1955 (Box 33, Folder 846)
  - Browne, Eliza E. (Estate), 1949-1953 (Box 33, Folder 847)
  - Bryant - Buck, 1946-1955 (Box 33, Folder 848)
  - Bugby - Burton, 1948-1958 (Box 33, Folder 849)
  - Burtt, 1945-1957 (Box 33, Folder 850)
  - Burweel - Cabot, 1945-1958 (Box 33, Folder 851)
  - Cadbury - Calder, 1945-1958 (Box 33, Folder 852)
  - Caldwell, Oliver J., 1952-1957 (Box 34, Folder 853)
  - California - Cameron, 1949-1958 (Box 34, Folder 854)
  - Camp - Campbell, 1948-1958 (Box 34, Folder 855)
  - Canales - Carhart, 1946-1958 (Box 34, Folder 856)
  - Carleton College - Carnahan, 1947-1958 (Box 34, Folder 857)
  - Carr, Alden J., 1956-1958 (Box 34, Folder 858-861)
  - Carroll, F. M., 1945-1955 (Box 34, Folder 862)
  - Carson, Arthur L., 1954-1958 (Box 34, Folder 863-866)
  - Cartwright, Frank T., 1949-1958, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 867-869)
  - Cary - Catapusan, 1955-1958 (Box 34, Folder 870)
  - Center Church - Chai, C., 1949-1958 (Box 34, Folder 871)
  - Chai, Martha May (Mei-Mei), 1953-1956 (Box 34, Folder 872)
  - Chamberlain - Chan, D., 1950-1958 (Box 34, Folder 873)
  - Chan, Hakchill, 1953-1956 (Box 34, Folder 874)
  - Chan, S. - Chang, D., 1945-1957 (Box 34, Folder 875)
  - Chang, Chi-Wen, 1946-1954 (Box 34, Folder 876)
  - Chang, C. - Chang, D., 1952-1958 (Box 34, Folder 877)
  - Chang, Frederick Hsui-Ming, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 878,879)
  - Chang, Fu-Liang, 1952-1956 (Box 35, Folder 880)
  - Chang, H. C. - Chang, H. H., 1947-1950 (Box 35, Folder 881)
  - Chang, James Lih-Yong, 1951-1958 (Box 35, Folder 882,883)
  - Chang, John - Chang, P., 1947-1955 (Box 35, Folder 884)
  - Chang, Shih-Chieh (John), 1952-1954 (Box 35, Folder 885)
  - Chang, Silas Hsien-Ta, 1952-1953 (Box 35, Folder 886,887)
  - Chang, Stephen S., 1955-1958 (Box 35, Folder 888)
  - Chang, Te Tzu, 1952-1954 (Box 35, Folder 889-891)
  - Chang, Tien-Teh, 1953-1955 (Box 35, Folder 892)
  - Chang, Timothy Hsien-Kuang, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 893)
  - Chang, Timothy Y. N. - Chang, Tse-Hua, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 894)
  - Chang, Vivien H.Y., 1952-1957 (Box 35, Folder 895)
  - Chang, Wei-ming, 1952-1958 (Box 35, Folder 896-898)
  - Chang, Yu-Ying, 1949-1953 (Box 35, Folder 899)
  - Change of Name, Petition for, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 900)
  - Chao, C. - Chao, D., 1946-1957 (Box 35, Folder 901)
  - Chao, Kwang-Chu, 1956-1958 (Box 35, Folder 902)
  - Chao, Peng-Lang, 1953-1956 (Box 35, Folder 903)
  - Chao, Shih-Chieh (Paul), 1952-1953 (Box 35, Folder 904)
  - Chao, Tsu-Chen, 1948-1956 (Box 35, Folder 905)
  - Chao, Wen-Ying, 1954-1957 (Box 35, Folder 906)
  - Chapman - Cheek, 1949-1957 (Box 35, Folder 907)
  - Cheeloo University: Bulletins and Letters, 1946-1953 (Box 35, Folder 908)
  - Cheeloo University: Conditions during Japanese Occupation, 1941-1947 (Box 36, Folder 909)
  - Cheeloo University: Reports of Medical School and Hospital, 1947-1950 (Box 36, Folder 910)
  - Cheeloo University: Reports of the President, 1946-1950 (Box 36, Folder 911)
  - Cheeloo University: Miscellaneous, 1945-1950 (Box 36, Folder 912)
  - Chen, A., 1947-1948 (Box 36, Folder 913)
  - Chen, Belle Pei-Li, 1952-1955 (Box 36, Folder 914,915)
  - Chen, C. - Chen, D., 1946-1958 (Box 36, Folder 916)
  - Chen, Edith I-Shu, 1953-1955 (Box 36, Folder 917,918)
  - Chen, H. - Chen, K., 1940-1956 (Box 36, Folder 919)
  - Chen, Lily, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 920)
  - Chen, Mary C. C., 1952-1955 (Box 36, Folder 921)
  - Chen, Min-Sun, 1952-1956 (Box 36, Folder 922,923)
  - Chen, Robert Long-Wen, 1949-1958 (Box 36, Folder 924-926)
  - Chen, R., 1945 (Box 36, Folder 927)
  - Chen, Shih-Chen (Samuel C.), 1947-1958 (Box 36, Folder 928,929)
  - Chen, Shu-Jen - Chen, T. Y., 1949-1958 (Box 36, Folder 930)
  - Chen, Theodore H. E., 1946-1958, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 931-936)
  - Chen, W., 1952-1956 (Box 36, Folder 937)
  - Chen, Yu-Gwan, 1945-1950 (Box 37, Folder 938, 939)
  - Chen, Yvonne Tze-Ming, 1953-1957 (Box 37, Folder 940)
  - Cheng, C. - Cheng, F., 1945-1957 (Box 37, Folder 941)
  - Cheng, L. - Cheng, O., 1945-1955 (Box 37, Folder 942)
  - Cheng, Paul (Pao-Lo), 1953-1958 (Box 37, Folder 943)
  - Cheng, T. - Cheng, Y., 1945-1956 (Box 37, Folder 944)
  - Chester, Ruth, 1947-1957 (Box 37, Folder 945)
  - Chiang - Chin, 1945-1958 (Box 37, Folder 947)
  - China Christian Colleges - China Christian Educational Association, 1931-1949 (Box 37, Folder 948)
  - China Christian Universities Association, 1945-1950 (Box 37, Folder 949)
  - China Institute in America, 1952-1956 (Box 37, Folder 950)
  - China Medical Board, 1945-1955 (Box 37, Folder 951)
  - China Tiffin Club - Chinese Advisory Committee on Cultural Relations, 1950-1958 (Box 37, Folder 952)
  - Chinese Student and Alumni Services (CSAS): Conferences, 1953-1956 (Box 37, Folder 953)
  - CSAS: Correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 37, Folder 954-957)
  - CSAS: Functions and Policies, 1952-1954, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 958)
  - CSAS: Minutes of Joint Committee, 1952-1955, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 959)
  - CSAS: Plans for Future, 1955-1957 (Box 38, Folder 960)
  - CSAS: Reports, 1952-1958 (Box 38, Folder 961-963)
  - Chou, E., 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 964)
  - Chou, Julia Wei-Hsien Wu, 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 965)
  - Chou, K., 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 966)
  - Chou, Leland Li-Chung, 1952-1957 (Box 38, Folder 967-969)
  - Chow - Christian Colleges in India: Statistics (Box 38, Folder 970)
  - Christian Medical Council for Overseas Work See: Morgan, Dr. Loren S. (Box 38, Folder 971)
  - Chu, Don-Chean, 1952-1954 (Box 38, Folder 972,973)
  - Chu, Feng-Ming See also: CSAS: Correspondence, for corres. 1955-1956., 1952-1955 Mar (Box 38, Folder 974-977)
  - Chu, Timothy Tin-Ru, 1952-1954 (Box 38, Folder 978)
  - Chu, Tung-Tsu, 1952-1954 (Box 38, Folder 979)
  - Chu, Yu-Kuang, 1953-1958 (Box 38, Folder 980-984)
  - Chung Kun Ai Foundation, 1951-1957 (Box 38, Folder 985)
  - Church Committee for Relief in Asia, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 986)
  - Church World Service, 1946-1950 (Box 38, Folder 987, 988)
  - Clark - Clarke, 1950-1958 (Box 39, Folder 989)
  - Clayton - Clise, 1949-1956 (Box 39, Folder 990)
  - Cochran, A. - Cochran, H., 1946-1953 (Box 39, Folder 991)
  - Cochran, Samuel and Cochran Memorial Fund, 1948-1958 (Box 39, Folder 992)
  - Cochran, Samuel, Jr. - Coe, A., 1953-1955 (Box 39, Folder 993)
  - Coe, John L., 1951-1958 (Box 39, Folder 994)
  - Coffin - Coggeshall, 1953-1956 (Box 39, Folder 995)
  - Cole, Theodore F., 1956-1957, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 996)
  - Coleman, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 997)
  - Coles, J. Ackerman (Estate), 1944-1954 (Box 39, Folder 998-1002)
  - Colley - Columbia Avenue Methodist Church, 1945-1957 (Box 39, Folder 1003)
  - Columbia University - Comfort, 1950-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1004)
  - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1005-1007)
  - Committee on Services in North America, 1953-1956 (Box 39, Folder 1008)
  - Committees (Regional) of the Associated Boards, ca.1939-1941, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1009)
  - Community Church - Congdon, 1946-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1010)
  - Consent to Use of Names by Wellesley-Yenching Committee, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 1011)
  - Consolidation, Petition for, 1945 May (Box 39, Folder 1012)
  - Constant - Cooke, 1945-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1013)
  - Cookingham - Cooley, 1946-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1014)
  - Copyright Registrations, 1954-1958 (Box 40, Folder 1015)
  - Corbett - Coulter, 1948-1958 (Box 40, Folder 1016)
  - Cox - Crary, 1946-1956 (Box 40, Folder 1017)
  - Crawford - Cressey, 1945-1955 (Box 40, Folder 1018)
  - Cressy, Earl H., 1945-1958 (Box 40, Folder 1019)
  - Crocker - Cross, L., 1949-1958 (Box 40, Folder 1020)
  - Cross, Rowland M., 1954-1958 (Box 40, Folder 1021-1025)
  - Crothers - Crumbacher, 1949-1956 (Box 40, Folder 1026)
  - Cunningham, Dr. Mrs. Edison R., 1947-1949 (Box 40, Folder 1027-1029)
  - Cunningham, J. - Curtis, 1945-1957 (Box 40, Folder 1030)
  - Cushman, Vera Scott (Estate), 1943-1953 (Box 40, Folder 1031, 1032)
  - Cutler - Danforth, 1943-1955 (Box 40, Folder 1033)
  - Daniels, J. Horton, 1945-1950 (Box 40, Folder 1034)
  - Davella Mills Foundation, 1946-1955 (Box 40, Folder 1035, 1036)
  - Davis - Dawson, 1949-1957 (Box 40, Folder 1037)
  - Day, Clarence B., 1946-1956 (Box 40, Folder 1038, 1039)
  - Day, L. - Day, M., 1950-1956 (Box 40, Folder 1040)
  - Dean, Samuel and Ruth, 1947-1954 (Box 41, Folder 1041)
  - de Beausset, Mrs. V. S. (Connie), 1953-1958 (Box 41, Folder 1042)
  - Decker, J. W., 1953-1957 (Box 41, Folder 1043)
  - DeGray, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 1044)
  - Delafield, Marsh and Hope, 1934-1956 (Box 41, Folder 1045-1047)
  - Den - Depkin, 1947-1950 (Box 41, Folder 1048)
  - de Vargas, Dr. and Mrs. Philip, 1945-1955 (Box 41, Folder 1049)
  - De Wolfe - Dickey, 1949-1958 (Box 41, Folder 1050)
  - Dickinson - Dingle (Box 41, Folder 1051)
  - Dirks, J. Edward, 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 1052)
  - Dixon - Dong (Box 41, Folder 1053)
  - Donham, Wallace B., 1946-1954 (Box 41, Folder 1054, 1055)
  - Donnell, 1946-1956 (Box 41, Folder 1056)
  - Drake, F. S., 1950-1952 (Box 41, Folder 1057)
  - Drury - Dugan, 1945-1957 (Box 41, Folder 1058)
  - Dulles - Dwight (Box 41, Folder 1059)
  - Dyson, J. W., 1946-1954 (Box 41, Folder 1060, 1061)
  - Eagan - East Bay Commmittee (Box 41, Folder 1062)
  - East China Union University, 1947-1950 (Box 41, Folder 1063)
  - Eastman - Ebbels, 1947-1956 (Box 41, Folder 1064)
  - Edwards, Dwight W., 1947-1958 (Box 41, Folder 1065-1067)
  - Eells - Elder, 1953-1958 (Box 41, Folder 1068)
  - Eley - Emory University (Box 41, Folder 1069)
  - Endicott - England, 1946-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1070)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: Cheeloo Univ., 1945-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1071)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: Fukien Christian University, 1946-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1072)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: Ginling, Hangchow, Huachung, 1945-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1073)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: Hwa Nan, Lingnan, 1946-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1074)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: Nanking, University of, 1946-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1075)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: St. John's, Soochow, 1948-1949 (Box 42, Folder 1076)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: West China Union University, 1945-1949 (Box 42, Folder 1077, 1078)
  - Enrollments, Faculty, etc.: Yenching Univ., 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 1079)
  - Enrollments, Summary: the 13 Christian Colleges in China, 1927-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1080)
  - Ensley - Evans, F. (Box 42, Folder 1081)
  - Evans, Mr. and Mrs. William H., 1950-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1082, 1083)
  - Evans, Murray and Mary, 1956-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1084)
  - Ewing - Fair, 1951-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1085)
  - Fairbank, John K., 1952-1957 (Box 42, Folder 1086)
  - Fairfield, Wynn C., 1953-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1087)
  - Famine Fund - Farley (Box 42, Folder 1088)
  - Farner - Farnham, 1952-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1089)
  - Farrior, S. C., 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 1090)
  - Faulkner, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 1091)
  - Faurot, Albert, 1950-1955 (Box 42, Folder 1092)
  - Federated Churches, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 1093)
  - Fellowships, 1946-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1094)
  - Fenn, Reginald, 1952-1958 (Box 42, Folder 1095)
  - Fenn, William P., 1945-1947 May (Box 42, Folder 1096-1098)
  - Fenn, William P., 1947 Jun-1958 (Box 43, Folder 1099-1123)
  - Ferguson, L., 1953-1954 (Box 44, Folder 1124)
  - Ferguson, Mary, 1952-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1125)
  - Ferris - Findlay, 1947-1957 (Box 44, Folder 1126)
  - Finley, Mrs. John H. (Martha Boyden), 1947-1957 (Box 44, Folder 1127)
  - Firor - First Methodist Church, 1947-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1128)
  - First Presbyterian Church - Fisher, E., 1955-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1129)
  - Fisher, J. - Fisken, 1946-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1130)
  - Fitch - Flagler, 1951-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1131)
  - Fleming, John R., 1952-1956 (Box 44, Folder 1132, 1133)
  - Fletcher, A. G., 1948-1955 (Box 44, Folder 1134)
  - Fletcher, T. - Fonda, 1947-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1135)
  - Fong, S. H., 1946-1959 (Box 44, Folder 1136, 1137)
  - Foo, Mei-Hua (May-Wo), 1952-1954 (Box 44, Folder 1138)
  - Forman Christian College - Found (Box 44, Folder 1139)
  - Frank, Henry S., 1947-1956 (Box 44, Folder 1140)
  - Franklin - Freeman, C., 1952-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1141)
  - Freeman, Mansfield, 1950-1958, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1141A)
  - Freeman, R. - Frei, 1948-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1142)
  - French, Clara M., 1954-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1142)
  - Friends Service Council (London), 1945-1955 (Box 44, Folder 1143)
  - Fries - Fugh (Box 44, Folder 1144)
  - Fukien Christian University: Assets, contributors, income, 1941-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1145)
  - College of Agriculture, 1946-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1145)
  - Fukien Christian University: Faculty lists and statistics; payroll, 1944-1948? (Box 44, Folder 1146)
  - Fukien Christian University: Graduating class, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 1146)
  - Fukien Christian University: Newsletter, 1951-1956 (Box 44, Folder 1147)
  - Fukien Christian University: Reports, 1941-1950 (Box 44, Folder 1148)
  - Fulbright Program, 1947-1948 (Box 45, Folder 1149)
  - Fuller - Galpin, 1946-1956 (Box 45, Folder 1150)
  - Galt - Gamble, 1945-1953 (Box 45, Folder 1151)
  - Gamewell - Garven (Box 45, Folder 1152)
  - Gates - Gench (Box 45, Folder 1153)
  - Geng, George, 1952-1957 (Box 45, Folder 1154-1156)
  - Gentry - Gilkey (Box 45, Folder 1157)
  - Gillespie Co. - Ginling Assets, 1945-1958 (Box 45, Folder 1158)
  - Ginling Association in America, 1951-1957 (Box 45, Folder 1159, 1160)
  - Ginling Association Newsletter, 1951-1958 (Box 45, Folder 1161, 1162)
  - Ginling Faculty Lists, 1938-1951, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1163)
  - Ginling Plays, 1940, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 1164)
  - Ginling Rehabilitation, 1946-1948 (Box 45, Folder 1165)
  - Ginling Reports, 1945-1954, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1166, 1167)
  - Ginling Student and Alumnae Statistics - Glenn, 1945-1958 (Box 45, Folder 1168)
  - Go Ti Swat, 1953-1956 (Box 45, Folder 1169-1171)
  - Godley - Goodrich, 1951-1958 (Box 45, Folder 1172)
  - Goucher, John F. (Estate), 1947-1952 (Box 46, Folder 1173)
  - Gowdy - Green (Box 46, Folder 1174)
  - Greene (Box 46, Folder 1175)
  - Griffin - Grose (Box 46, Folder 1176)
  - Gross - Haley (Box 46, Folder 1177)
  - Hall (Box 46, Folder 1178)
  - Hamill - Hancock, 1945-1958 (Box 46, Folder 1179)
  - Hangchow Christian College (Hangchow Univ.), 1945-1951, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1180)
  - Hannah - Harmon, 1946-1957 (Box 46, Folder 1181)
  - Harrison - Hartford Seminary Foundation, 1949-1956 (Box 46, Folder 1182)
  - Hartford Seminary Campus Chest - Harvard University Library, 1950-1953 (Box 46, Folder 1183)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Fukien Christian University Reports, 1946-1951 (Box 46, Folder 1184)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Funds for Rehabilitation and other Emergencies, 1946-1950 (Box 46, Folder 1185)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Hua Chung University Report, 1944-1945 (Box 46, Folder 1186)
  - Lingnan University Report, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 1186)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: University of Nanking Reports, 1945-1950 (Box 46, Folder 1187)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Peiping Office Report, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 1188)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Policy and Procedure, 1951, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1189)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Projects, 1952-1958 (Box 46, Folder 1190, 1191)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Shantung University Report, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 1192)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: West China Union University Reports, 1945-1950 (Box 46, Folder 1192)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Trustees Meetings, 1949-1950 (Box 46, Folder 1193)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute: Yenching University Reports, 1945-1950 (Box 46, Folder 1194)
  - Harvey, 1949-1957 (Box 46, Folder 1195)
  - Hausserman - Headley (Box 46, Folder 1196)
  - Heard - Hickox (Box 47, Folder 1197)
  - Higgins - Hirst (Box 47, Folder 1198)
  - Ho, C. - Ho, J., 1950-1957 (Box 47, Folder 1199)
  - Ho, Kenneth, 1953-1954 (Box 47, Folder 1200)
  - Ho, W. - Hoffsommer, 1946-1957 (Box 47, Folder 1201)
  - Hoh, Fay, 1954-1955 (Box 47, Folder 1202)
  - Holden - Holton (Box 47, Folder 1203)
  - Hon, Sammy C. Y., 1953-1958 (Box 47, Folder 1204, 1205)
  - Hoobler - Hoover, F., 1943-1958 (Box 47, Folder 1206)
  - Hoover, L. - Horton, 1952-1958 (Box 47, Folder 1207)
  - Hou - Hough, L. H., 1947-1958 (Box 47, Folder 1208)
  - Hough Trust Fund (Mrs. L. M. Hough), 1948-1950 (Box 47, Folder 1209)
  - How - Hsiao (Box 47, Folder 1210)
  - Hsieh, Raymond Hsin-Ching (Zia, Raymond), 1952-1955 (Box 47, Folder 1211-1213)
  - Hsieh - Hsu, C., 1950-1955 (Box 47, Folder 1214)
  - Hsu, D. - Hsu, P., 1946-1957 (Box 47, Folder 1215)
  - Hsu, Shiu-Ying, 1953-1955 (Box 47, Folder 1216)
  - Hsu, Shu-hsi - Hsueh (Box 47, Folder 1217)
  - Hu, Ian Y. C., 1952-1956 (Box 47, Folder 1218)
  - Hu, S. - Hu, Y., 1955-1958 (Box 47, Folder 1219)
  - Huachung University: Annual Reports, 1945-1951 (Box 48, Folder 1220, 1221)
  - Huachung University: Financial Statements, 1948-1951 (Box 48, Folder 1222)
  - Huachung Universtiy: Newsletter, 1948-1951 (Box 48, Folder 1223, 1224)
  - Huachung University: Ten Year Plan, 1944, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1224A)
  - Huachung University: Transfer of Funds to the United Board, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 1225)
  - Huang, Allen Tzu-chuan, 1955-1959 (Box 48, Folder 1226)
  - Huang, Chen-jung, 1951-1958 (Box 48, Folder 1227, 1228)
  - Huang, Chen-ya, 1952-1955 (Box 48, Folder 1229)
  - Huang, Chia-teh - Huang, Chu-yih, 1949-1955 (Box 48, Folder 1230)
  - Huang, David, 1955-1957 (Box 48, Folder 1231)
  - Huang, G. - Huang, N., 1952-1955 (Box 48, Folder 1232)
  - Huang, Robert T., 1953-1955 (Box 48, Folder 1233)
  - Huang, Y. - Huff, 1946-1958 (Box 48, Folder 1234)
  - Huggins - Humphreys (Box 48, Folder 1235)
  - Hung, Frederick, 1952-1955 (Box 48, Folder 1236, 1237)
  - Hung, William, 1945-1958 (Box 48, Folder 1238)
  - Hunter, Mr. and Mrs. James A., 1950-1958 (Box 48, Folder 1239)
  - Hunter, R. - Hussey, 1949-1956 (Box 48, Folder 1240)
  - Hutchings, Francis S., 1952-1957 (Box 48, Folder 1241)
  - Hutchins, M. - Hwa Nan College: Assets, 1945-1947, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1242)
  - Hwa Nan College: Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 48, Folder 1243)
  - Hwang, Cheng-Hoe, 1954-1958 (Box 48, Folder 1244)
  - Hwang, S. - Illick, 1950-1957 (Box 48, Folder 1245)
  - Immanuel Congregational Church - Indianapolis Smith Club, 1949-1957 (Box 49, Folder 1246)
  - Indonesian Christian University, 1953-1958 (Box 49, Folder 1247)
  - Indonesian Council of Churches - Inglis, 1950-1956 (Box 49, Folder 1248)
  - Insurance Data: All Universities (Box 49, Folder 1249, 1250)
  - Insurance Data: Fukien Christian University, 1936, 1950, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1251)
  - Insurance Data: Ginling College, 1924-1951 (Box 49, Folder 1252)
  - Insurance Data: Hangchow Christian College, 1942-1951, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1253)
  - Insurance Data: Hwa Nan College, 1945-1951 (Box 49, Folder 1254)
  - Insurance Data: University of Nanking, 1941-1944, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1255)
  - Insurance Data: Shantung Christian University (Cheeloo), 1932, 1951, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1256)